/**
 * Created by IDIMMA on 8/18/2017.
 */
function loadquestion() {
    var questiondata = {
        "question1": [
            {
                "question": "WHAT DOES THE NAME \"MOSES\" MEAN?",
                "opts": [
                    " I SAVED HIM FROM WATER",
                    "PRINCE SAVED FROM THE NILE",
                    "I DREW HIM FROM WATER",
                    "I DREW HIM FROM DEATH"
                ],
                "answer": "I DREW HIM FROM WATER",
                "bible_ref": "EXO 2:10,"
            },
            {
                "question": "WHAT WAS PAUL\'S  ANTIDOTE TO ANXIETY?",
                "opts": [
                    "CHANGE YOUR THINKING",
                    "PRAYER, SUPPLICATION AND THANKGIVING",
                    "LET YOUR MODERATION BE KNOWN BY ALL MEN",
                    "PUT ON THE WHOLE ARMOUR OF GOD"
                ],
                "answer": "PRAYER, SUPPLICATION AND THANKGIVING",
                "bible_ref": "PHIL 2:6"
            },
            {
                "question": "IN WHAT SITUATION DID PAUL SAY HE HAD LEARNED TO SHOW CONTENT?",
                "opts": [
                    "WHEN HE WAS HEALTHY",
                    "WHEN THE LORD BLESSES HIM WITH A GIFT",
                    "WHEN HE HAD NON",
                    "WHATEVER THE CIRCUMSTANCE"
                ],
                "answer": "WHATEVER THE CIRCUMSTANCE",
                "bible_ref": "PHIL 4:11-12"
            },
            {
                "question": "HOW OLD WAS SAMUEL WHEN HIS MOTHER TOOK HIM TO THE TEMPLE TO LIVE?",
                "opts": [
                    "WHEN HE HAD BEEN WEANED",
                    "WHEN HE HAD BEEN CIRCUMCISED",
                    "WHEN HE WAS 8 DAYS OLD",
                    "WHEN HE WAS 12 YEAR OLD"
                ],
                "answer": "WHEN HE HAD BEEN WEANED",
                "bible_ref": "1 SAM 2:22"
            },
            {
                "question": "WHO WROTE BOOK OF ACTS OF THE APOSTLE?",
                "opts": [
                    "LUKE",
                    "MARK",
                    "PAUL",
                    "SALIAS"
                ],
                "answer": "LUKE",
                "bible_ref": "ACTS 1:1"
            },
            {
                "question": "WHEN PETER CAME TO LYDDA HE FOUND A CERTAIN MAN NAMED AENEAS WHO WAS BEDRIDDEN",
                "opts": [
                    "38 YEARS",
                    "8 YEARS",
                    "28 YEARS",
                    "18 YEARS"
                ],
                "answer": "38 YEARS",
                "bible_ref": "ACTS "
            },
            {
                "question": "WHERE DID SOLOMON BUILD THE TEMPLE OF THE LORD?",
                "opts": [
                    "ON MOUNT ZION",
                    "IN THE CITY OF JERUSALEM",
                    "ON MOUNT MORIAH",
                    "IN THE LAND OF JUDAH"
                ],
                "answer": "ON MOUNT MORIAH",
                "bible_ref": "2 CHR 3:1"
            },
            {
                "question": "WHO HAD JEREMIAH THE PROPHET BEATEN AND PUT INTO WOODEN STOCKS?",
                "opts": [
                    "PASHHUR, THE PRIEST AND CHIEF GOVERNOR",
                    "THOSE WHO WORSHIPPED IDOLS,HIS OWN FRIENDS",
                    "HIS OWN CHILDREN",
                    "HIS OWN FRIENDS"
                ],
                "answer": "PASHHUR, THE PRIEST AND CHIEF GOVERNOR",
                "bible_ref": "JER 20:2"
            },
            {
                "question": "FILL IN THE IN THE BLANKS \"BEHOLD UPON THE MOUNTAIN THE_________OF HIM THAT BRINGETH GOOD TIDINGS THAT PUBLISHETH_________!\"",
                "opts": [
                    "FACE, JOY",
                    "FORM, WAR",
                    "HOPE, THE GOSPLE",
                    "FEET, PEACE"
                ],
                "answer": "FEET, PEACE ",
                "bible_ref": "NAH 1:15"
            },
            {
                "question": "MY NAME IS: MAHERSHALALHASHBAZ, WHO AM I?",
                "opts": [
                    "PROPHET ISAIAH\'S FIRST SON",
                    "PROPHET ISAIAH\'S SECOND SON",
                    "PROPHET ISAIAH\'S THIRD SON",
                    "PROPHET ISAIAH\'S FOURTH SON"
                ],
                "answer": "PROPHET ISAIAH\'S SECOND SON",
                "bible_ref": "IS 8:3"
            }],
        "question2": [
            {
                "question": "THE NAME OF THE FIRST RIVER MENTION IN THE BIBLE IS?",
                "opts": [
                    "GIHON",
                    "HIDDEKEL",
                    "PISON",
                    "EUPHRATES"
                ],
                "answer": "PISON",
                "bible_ref": "GEN 2:11"
            },
            {
                "question": "ACCORDING TO JOHN\'S DESCRIPTION OF THE NEW JERUSALEM IN REVELATION, WHAT IS MISSING IN THE CITY?",
                "opts": [
                    "THE PALACE",
                    "THE TEMPLE",
                    "THE ARK",
                    "DWELLING PLACES"
                ],
                "answer": "THE TEMPLE",
                "bible_ref": "REV 21:22"
            },
            {
                "question": "WHAT IS THE BABYLONIAN NAME GIVEN TO DANIEL",
                "opts": [
                    "BELSHAZZAR",
                    "BELFARZAR",
                    "BELTESHAZZAR",
                    "AZARIAH"
                ],
                "answer": "BELTESHAZZAR",
                "bible_ref": "DAN 1:7"
            },
            {
                "question": "WHICH AMONG THIS CHURCHES IN REVELATION HAVE THE DOCTRINE OF BALAAM",
                "opts": [
                    "SMYRNA",
                    "SARDIS",
                    "PERGAMOS",
                    "THYATRIA"
                ],
                "answer": "PERGAMOS",
                "bible_ref": "REV 2:14"
            },
            {
                "question": "WHICH AMONG THESE CHURCHES DID JESUS COULD NOT FIND FAULT IN",
                "opts": [
                    "PHILADELPHIA",
                    "SARDIS",
                    "SMYRNA",
                    "LAODICEA"
                ],
                "answer": "PHILADELPHIA",
                "bible_ref": "REV 3:7-13"
            },
            {
                "question": "ACCORDING TO REVELATION TO WHICH CHURCH DID JESUS INTRODUCED HIMSELF AS \"HE THAT OPENTH, AND NO MAN CAN SHUTTETH;\"?",
                "opts": [
                    "THYATIRA",
                    "EPHESUS",
                    "PHILADELPHIA",
                    "SARDIS"
                ],
                "answer": "PHILADELPHIA",
                "bible_ref": "REV 3:7"
            },
            {
                "question": "WHO WROTE THE BOOK OF TITUS",
                "opts": [
                    "PAUL",
                    "TITUS",
                    "PETER",
                    "JOHN THE BELOVETH"
                ],
                "answer": "PAUL",
                "bible_ref": "TITUS 1:1"
            },
            {
                "question": "THERE ARE HOW MANY GIFTS OF THE SPIRIT?",
                "opts": [
                    "3 GIFTS",
                    "7 GIFTS",
                    "9 GIFTS",
                    "12 GIFTS"
                ],
                "answer": "9 GIFTS",
                "bible_ref": "1 COR 12:1-11"
            },
            {
                "question": "FILL IN THE BLANK: A GOOD NAME IS BETTER THAN ___________?",
                "opts": [
                    "SILVER AND GOLD",
                    "DIAMOND AND RICHES",
                    "PRECIOUS OINTMENT",
                    "ONITMENT OF FAME"
                ],
                "answer": "PRECIOUS OINTMENT",
                "bible_ref": "ECC 7:1"
            },
            {
                "question": "THE BIBLE VERSE \"THE SACRIFIES OF GOD ARE A BROKEN SPIRIT: A BROKEN SPIRIT AND A CONTRITE HEART, OH GOD, THOU WILT NOT DESPISE\" CAN BE FOUND IN?",
                "opts": [
                    "PSALM 115 VS 2",
                    "PSALM 51 VS 17",
                    "PSALM 55 VS 12",
                    "PSALM 25 VS 5"
                ],
                "answer": "PSALM 51 VS 17",
                "bible_ref": "PSALM 51 VS 17"
            },
        ],
        "question3": [

            {
                "question": "THE BIBLE CAPTION \"CAST ME NOT AWAY FROM THY PRESENCE AND TAKE NOT THY HOLY SPIRIT FROM ME\" CAN BE FOUND IN WHICH OF THESE BIBLE VERSES?",
                "opts": [
                    "PSALM 51 VS 9",
                    "PSALM 51 VS 11",
                    "PSALM 51 VS 12",
                    "PSALM 51 VS 17"
                ],
                "answer": "PSALM 51 VS 12",
                "bible_ref": "PSALM 51 VS 12"
            },
            {
                "question": "WHO WROTE THE BOOK OF LAMENTATION",
                "opts": [
                    "KING HEZEKIAH",
                    "HOSEA",
                    "JEREMIAH",
                    "KING JOSIAH"
                ],
                "answer": "JEREMIAH",
                "bible_ref": "2 CHR 35:25"
            },
            {
                "question": "HOW MANY TIMES DID PUAL THE APOSTLE SUFFER SHIPWRECK",
                "opts": [
                    "7 TIMES",
                    "4 TIMES",
                    "3 TIMES",
                    "2 TIMES"
                ],
                "answer": "3 TIMES",
                "bible_ref": "2 COR 11:25"
            },
            {
                "question": "FOR WE CAN DO NOTHING AGAINST THE TRUTH, BUT FOR THE TRUTH CAN BE FOUND IN WHICH OF THESE VERSES?",
                "opts": [
                    "GAL 6:14",
                    "2 COR 13:8",
                    "ROM 5:9",
                    "EPH 2:11"
                ],
                "answer": "2 COR 13:8",
                "bible_ref": "2 COR 13:8"
            },
            {
                "question": "FILL IN BLANKS  \"I AM ________ WITH CHRIST NEVERTHELESS I LIVE ; YET NOT I BUT _______ LIVETH IN ME:\"",
                "opts": [
                    "RESURRECTED, JESUS",
                    "BURIED, CHRIST",
                    "CRUCIFIED, CHRIST",
                    "CRUCIFIED, HOLYSPIRIT"
                ],
                "answer": "CRUCIFIED, CHRIST",
                "bible_ref": "GAL 2:22"
            },
            {
                "question": "WHO ADVICED THE RELIGIOUS LEADER TO REFRAIN FROM THE APOSTLE BY SAYING \"IF THERE COUNSEL BE OF MAN IT WILL COME TO NOUGHT \"?",
                "opts": [
                    "GAMALIEL",
                    "ALEXANDER",
                    "CAIAPHAS",
                    "THEUDAS"
                ],
                "answer": "GAMALIEL",
                "bible_ref": "ACTS 5:34-39"
            },
            {
                "question": "WHICH AMONG THESE CHURCHES JESUS TOLD HE WILL SPUE OF HIS MOUTH?",
                "opts": [
                    "SARDIS",
                    "LAODICEA",
                    "PERGAMOS",
                    "SMYRNA"
                ],
                "answer": "LAODICEA",
                "bible_ref": "REV 3:16"
            },
            {
                "question": "ACCORDING TO THE BOOK OF REVELATION, ______ HAST THEM THAT HOLDS THE DOCTRINE OF THE NICOLAITANES?",
                "opts": [
                    "PHILADELPHIA",
                    "EPHESUS",
                    "PERGAMOS",
                    "THYATIRA"
                ],
                "answer": "PERGAMOS",
                "bible_ref": "REV 2:15"
            },
            {
                "question": "HOW OLD WAS REHOBOAM WHEN HE BECAME KING?",
                "opts": [
                    "39 YEARS",
                    "40 YEARS",
                    "41 YEARS",
                    "42 YEARS"
                ],
                "answer": "40 YEARS",
                "bible_ref": "1 KINGS 14:21"
            },
            {
                "question": "ADONIJAH WAS EXECUTED BY WHICH OF THESE KINGS?",
                "opts": [
                    "KING DAVID",
                    "KING SOLOMON",
                    "KING REHOBOAM",
                    "KING JEROBOAM"
                ],
                "answer": "KING SOLOMON",
                "bible_ref": "1 KINGS 2:13-23"
            },
        ],
        "question4": [
            {
                "question": "IN WHAT YEAR DID DANIEL RECIEVE HIS SECOND VISION?",
                "opts": [
                    "THIRD YEAR OF BELSHAZZAR\'S REIGN",
                    "SECOND YEAR OF NEBUCHADNEZZAR\'S REIGN",
                    "FIRST YEAR OF DARIUS\'S REIGN",
                    "FIRST YEAR OF BELSHAZZAR\'S REIGN"
                ],
                "answer": "THIRD YEAR OF BELSHAZZAR\'S REIGN",
                "bible_ref": "DAN 8:1"
            },
            {
                "question": "IN WHAT YEAR DID DANIEL RECIEVE HIS FIRST VISION?",
                "opts": [
                    "IN THE YEAR KING UZZIAH DIED",
                    "SECOND YEAR OF NEBUCHADNEZZAR\'S REIGN",
                    "FIRST YEAR OF DARIUS\'S REIGN",
                    "FIRST YEAR OF BELSHAZZAR\'S REIGN"
                ],
                "answer": "FIRST YEAR OF BELSHAZZAR\'S REIGN",
                "bible_ref": "DAN 7:1"
            },
            {
                "question": "SOLOMON REIGNED OVER ISREAL FOR HOW MANY YEARS?",
                "opts": [
                    "30 YEARS",
                    "35 YEARS",
                    "37 YEARS",
                    "40 YEARS"
                ],
                "answer": "40 YEARS",
                "bible_ref": "2 CHR 9:30"
            },
            {
                "question": "THE NAME OF THE FIRST RIVER MENTION IN THE BIBLE IS?",
                "opts": [
                    "GIHON",
                    "PISON",
                    "HIDDEKEL",
                    "EUPHRATES"
                ],
                "answer": "PISON",
                "bible_ref": "GEN 2:11"
            },
            {
                "question": "______ AND _______ WERE CREATED ON THE FIRST DAY?",
                "opts": [
                    "DAY AND NIGHT",
                    "LIGHT AND DARKNESS",
                    "MOON AND STAR",
                    "SUN AND MOON"
                ],
                "answer": "DAY AND NIGHT",
                "bible_ref": "GEN 1:3-5"
            },
            {
                "question": "ON THE SECOND DAY OF CREATION GOD SAID ........",
                "opts": [
                    "LET THERE BE A FIRMAMENT IN THE MIDST OF THE SKY",
                    "LET THERE BE A FIRMAMENT IN THE MIDST OF THE WATERS",
                    "LET THERE BE HEAVENS IN THE MIDST OF THE FIRMAMENT",
                    "LET THE WATERS UNDER THE HEAVENS BE GATHERED TOGETHER IN ONE PLACE"
                ],
                "answer": "LET THERE BE A FIRMAMENT IN THE MIDST OF THE WATERS",
                "bible_ref": "GEN 1:6"
            },
            {
                "question": "THE FIRMAMENT DIVIDED?",
                "opts": [
                    "THE HEAVENS FROM THE HEAVEN",
                    "THE HEAVENS FROM THE EARTH",
                    "THE WATERS FROM THE WATERS",
                    "THE WATERS FROM THE EARTH"
                ],
                "answer": "THE WATERS FROM THE WATERS",
                "bible_ref": "GEN 1:6"
            },
            {
                "question": "AND THE SPIRIT OF GOD WAS HOVERING OVER THE FACE OF THE______?",
                "opts": [
                    "DEEP",
                    "WATERS",
                    "DARKNESS",
                    "VOID"
                ],
                "answer": "WATERS",
                "bible_ref": "GEN 1:2"
            },
            {
                "question": "WHICH OF THESE WAS NOT DONE ON THE THIRD DAY OF CREATION?",
                "opts": [
                    "THE GATHERING TOGETHER OF THE WATER UNDER THE FIRMAMENT",
                    "THE BRINGING FORTH OF GRASS HERB THAT YIELD SEEDS BY THE EARTH ",
                    "THE CREATION OF LIGHT IN THE FIRMAMENT",
                    "THE CREATION OF DRY LAND"
                ],
                "answer": "THE CREATION OF LIGHT IN THE FIRMAMENT",
                "bible_ref": "GEN 1:9-13"
            },
            {
                "question": "THE STARS WERE ON THE ______ DAY OF CREATION?",
                "opts": [
                    "THIRD",
                    "FOURTH",
                    "FIFTH",
                    "SIXTH"
                ],
                "answer": "FOURTH",
                "bible_ref": "Gen 1:16-18"
            },
            ],
        "question5": [
            {
                "question": "BIRDS AND LIVING CREATURES IN THE SEA WERE MADE ON THE __________ OF CREATION",
                "opts": [
                    "THIRD DAY",
                    "FOURTH DAY",
                    "FIFTH DAY",
                    "SIXTH DAY"
                ],
                "answer": "FIFTH DAY",
                "bible_ref": "GEN 1:20-23"
            },
            {
                "question": "\"LET MAKE MAN IN OUR IMAGE\", WAS SAID BY GOD ON THE",
                "opts": [
                    "SEVENTH DAY",
                    "FOURTH DAY",
                    "FIFTH DAY",
                    "SIXTH DAY"
                ],
                "answer": "SIXTH DAY",
                "bible_ref": "GEN 1:26-31"
            },
            {
                "question": "ON _______ GOD ENDED HIS WORK WHICH HE HAD DONE;",
                "opts": [
                    "SEVENTH DAY",
                    "FOURTH DAY",
                    "FIFTH DAY",
                    "SIXTH DAY"
                ],
                "answer": "SEVENTH DAY",
                "bible_ref": "GEN 2:2"
            },
            {
                "question": "GOD ______ THE SEVENTH DAY AND _______ IT",
                "opts": [
                    "\"RESTED ON\"  \"BLESSED\"",
                    "\"RESTED ON\" \"SANCTIFIED\"",
                    "\"JUSTIFIED\" \"SANCTIFIED\"",
                    "\"BLESSED\" \"SANCTIFIED\""
                ],
                "answer": "\"BLESSED\" \"SANCTIFIED\"",
                "bible_ref": "GEN 2:3"
            },
            {
                "question": "_______ WAS NOT LISTED WITH THE SEVEN DEACONS?",
                "opts": [
                    "PROCHORUS",
                    "NICANOR",
                    "TIMON",
                    "THEUDAS"
                ],
                "answer": "THEUDAS",
                "bible_ref": "ACTS 6:5"
            },
            {
                "question": "PAUL AND BARNABAS BEGAN THE PREACHING OF THE WORD OF GOD AT ________?",
                "opts": [
                    "SELEUCIA",
                    "PAPHOS",
                    "SALAMIS",
                    "ATTALIA"
                ],
                "answer": "SALAMIS",
                "bible_ref": "ACTS 13:4-5"
            },
            {
                "question": "AFTER THE DEATH OF STEPHEN AND PERSECUTIONS IN JERUSALEM,  PHILIP WENT DOWN TO? ",
                "opts": [
                    "SAMARIA",
                    "JUDEA",
                    "CAESAREA",
                    "AZOTUS"
                ],
                "answer": "SAMARIA",
                "bible_ref": "ACTS 8:5"
            }
        ]
    };
    return questiondata;
}